谢谢你们来到我的办公室见我
Thank you for seeing me in my office.
谢谢你开车带我们来
Thank you for the ride.
那是  我觉得在这了谈心会更加舒适
Well, I thought we would be more comfortable here.
而你们看见我所有的学历和证书时
And I thought you'd be more receptive to my words
也能更好的听进我的话
if you could see all my degrees.
总之  维罗不会投球了
So, Willow can't pitch.
对极了  治好她
Exactly. Fix her.
那么你就告诉我这幅罗夏测试图
So you tell me what is the first thing
（罗夏测试：通过墨迹图来反映被测者心理状况）
在你脑中最像什么
that pops into your head.
（墨迹图为左右对称，剧中测试方法不规范）
乔伊
Joey.
乔伊在骑一匹长得像乔伊的马
Joey on a horse that looks like Joey.
好了
Okay.
我看来要大胆推测
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
认定这其中肯定和乔伊
and say that this has something
有密不可分的联系
to do with Joey.
哇  你真在行
Wow, you're good.
乔伊
Joey?
这一切都是关于乔伊的
This whole thing is about Joey?
玛蒂  在这里我们要心平气和
Maddie, this is a safe place.
不要随意给别人下定论
We do not judge,
哪怕这是你脑中
even if it is the first place
第一个想去的地方
your brain wants to go.
那么你和乔伊到底是什么关系
Okay, so what is going on with you and Joey?
没任何关系  这就是症结了
Nothing. That's the problem.
正是春意盎然之时
It's springtime.
爱意弥漫在空中  鸟儿在枝头谈情说爱
Love is in the air, birds are chirping,
可我魂牵梦绕的一切就是
but all I can think about is
为何我的小乔伊不跟我谈情说爱啊
why doesn't my sweet little Joey bird chirp at me?
那到底乔伊和你的投球有什么关系
Okay, what... what does Joey have to do with your pitching?
我集中不了注意力
I can't concentrate.
当我投球时 我直视着你
When I pitch, I look directly at you.
- 对的  - 但我每次看你
- Right. - But every time I look at you,
脑中就浮现出乔伊
all I see is Joey.
我长得像乔伊  不可能
I look like Joey?! No, okay.
我们都戴眼镜
We both wear glasses,
可这就是唯一的相同点了  好不
but that is where the similarity ends, right?
对不
Right?!
所以你投球水平这么烂
So the reason you stink at pitching
责任在我头上
is because of me?
对  你们俩长得简直像极了
Yeah. You guys look exactly like each other.
只不过他才能打动我
Except he makes it work.